# **MORGAN KIGER**

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

#### • DETAILS •

mkiger95@gmail.com

• SKILLS •

**SQL** Database

Creative Thinker

**Cloud Computing** 

Agile Methodologies

**Amazon Web Services** 

Linux/Command Prompt

**Efficient Time Management** 

**Requires Minimal Supervision** 

• LINKS •

**Github** 

LinkedIn

www.morgankiger.com

**AWS Developer Associate Cert** 

## PROFILE

I am a software developer with cloud experience. I have 4 **years of experience** in developing, automation, data reconciliation, SQL databases, AWS, and more. Over the years I have led and delivered successful agile-structured projects.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

#### AWS Contractor at Self-Employed, Las Vegas

June 2020 — Present

- Developed lambda functions to automated work within AWS, some functions worked acrossed multiple accounts
- used cloudwatch to set up alarms to trigger lambda functions
- · created lambda functions to consolidate logs from multiple accounts to a master account

#### Software Developer at Bonotel Exlcusive Travel

October 2018 — May 2020

- Coded automation for data entry process within the business using selenium
- Coded an automated inventory check that checks availability for all active hotels weekly, improved visibility into the company's inventory problem
- Worked with aws resources like ec2, s3, lambda, cloudwatch, and more
- Coded an automated data recon between our booking database and billing application/database, improving billing discrepancies
- Built the frontend(JS React)/backend(GoLang) for an internal tool to check supplier rates/download ean content

#### IT Intern at Bonotel Exclusive Travel

December 2015 — October 2018

- Mapped hotels to our system, to create a real-time connection for rates
- · Supported all of internal staff with anything tech related

## **Shift Manager at Sweet Addiction**

August 2012 — May 2014

- While in high school, I would manage the store and the employees
- · Supervised staff and handled all customer service issues
- Handled all money/till at the end of the day, ultimately ran the shop

#### EDUCATION

### Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering, University of Nevada Las Vegas

August 2014 — May 2020

- Minor in Computer Science and Mathematics
- Member of Lambda Chi Alpha
  - Held position: President, Secretary, Alumni Relations

#### **REFERENCES**

References available upon request